(ｶﾗｽの鳴き声)
(みはりの鼻歌)
(まひろ)ん んっ｡
(戦闘ｹﾞｰﾑ音)
(みはりの鼻歌)
(まひろ)んっ んっ んぃ…｡
(戦闘ｹﾞｰﾑ音)
(みはりの鼻歌)
(しずくの音)
ﾆﾋﾋ…｡
(戦闘ｹﾞｰﾑ音)
(みはりの鼻歌)
(みはり)きゃああ～！
(まひろ)えっ な なんだ!?
Wh-What happened?!
What's here is gone
What's gone is here
Today a cucumber, tomorrow a clam
Gotta check my trousers, trance, trance, trance
What's his is gone
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
What's hers is here
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
My pronouns are in shambles!
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Gone are the days of making wagies seethe
oyama Mahiro
(Bye-bye alright! I'm still unemployable!)
oyama Mihari
Without balls I just can't get up for it
(Scratch that, grow a pair! I won't stand for this!)
Ah, having peered into a queer new world
I've been bewitched by its siren song
I dove right in and the water's great
Cute outfits, makeup galore, and hairstyles aplenty
The world of women is calling my name
Wait, I'm a dude! Or am I?
(Are!)
(Who!)
Some part of my identity is crumbling
(It's me!)
Leading to a newborn sense of wonder
As an unknown sensation pervades my psyche
Awaken, my inner cute girl!
With proper stimulation comes a happy ending?
What's here is gone
What's gone is here
Today a cucumber, tomorrow a clam
Gotta check my trousers, trance, trance, trance
What's his is gone
What's hers is here
My manhood's in total shambles!
The water heater's broken?
Yeah, the water's cold.
#fdfdfc Mahiro's Time of the Month
You're a genius scientist, aren't you?
Can't you fix it?
This isn't my area of expertise.
風呂が壊れた？
Welp, guess we're not taking baths today, then!
(みはり)お湯が出ないみたいなの｡
Not a chance!
お前 天才科学者だろ｡
直せないの？
Hang on! Isn't there a public bath near us?
そういうのは ちょっと…｡
ｶﾊ～！
Oh yeah, that one across from the liquor store?
じゃあ今日は 入らなくていいな！
ﾀﾞﾒよ そんなの！
ｶﾞﾌ…｡
Well, go get ready. I'm gonna go get dressed.
そうだ！ 近くに
お風呂屋さんがあるでしょ｡
Aww...
あ～ たしか 酒屋の向かいに…｡
じゃあ 準備してね
私も着替えるから｡
ええ～｡
A public bath, huh?
Wait a sec!
Don't you think that's a bad idea?!
(扉の開閉音)
銭湯ねぇ…｡
W-Welp, guess we're here...
んっ？ っておい！
それはまずいだろ！
Come on, Onii-chan. What's keeping you?
C-Coming...
け 結局来てしまったが…｡
何してるの お兄ちゃん｡ 行くよ！
おお… おう…｡
んん～｡
んっ うぃ…｡
Women
Uh...
Men
Well, see you later.
Wait, stop!
うう～ うう…｡
Where are you going?!
C-Come on, Mihari!
Men
ええっと…｡
I can't just waltz into the women's baths!
Who cares? You're a girl now, anyway.
じゃ あとで！
Hello, welcome!
ちょっとちょっと どこ行くの！
えぇ～｡
Entry for two, please.
だ だってお前
やっぱ さすがに女湯は…｡
And your change.
いいじゃん 今は女の子なんだし｡
う ううぇ｡
Women
(番台)はい いらっしゃい｡
はう うぅ…｡
B-But wait!
２人分お願いします｡
Well, whatever.
If Mihari's fine with it...
(番台)あいよ｡
If she says it's okay...
え で でも…｡
《いやしかし
みはりがいいって言うなら…｡
いいって 言うなら…》
Yup, looks about right.
Sorry to disappoint.
うん 知ってた…｡
(鈴の音)
残念でした｡
So, I don't care if people see me.
But what about you?
ふん ん… んん～ んっ！
Huh? Why do you ask?
Q-Q-Quit staring at me!
いや 俺は別にいいんだけどさ…｡
Relax. I couldn't care less about seeing my sister naked.
お前はどうなの？
へっ？ なんで私？
はっ！
ああ あんまり見ないでね!?
んっ 妹の裸には興味ないで～す｡
Wow, this place is awesome!
んん～｡
(戸を開ける音)
It's bigger than I thought it was gonna be!
ふん！
おお～ さすが銭湯～！
Hey, look! They have spa jets!
思ったより 広いな～！
Come back here! We have to shower first!
むぅ～｡
ｳﾊﾊﾊ！
Yes, ma'am...
ｼﾞｪｯﾄがあるぞ～！ ｱﾊﾊ！
Umph.
うんん！
こら！
うぇ!?
体 洗ってから！
は～い…｡
よっこいしょっと…｡ ん…｡
All done.
～
Stop right there!
What? I showered, didn't I?
Your hair's longer now!
You've gotta be more thorough!
ぶへぇ｡
Here, now's as good a time as any.
お先～｡
え 待って待って！
Let me show you how it's done.
ちゃんと洗っただろぉ｡
Uh oh...
髪の毛 長いんだから
そんなんじゃﾀﾞﾒ！
First, brush out your hair to remove any build-up.
いいわ この際だし｡
うわ…｡
You should really do this before it's wet, but just remember for next time, okay?
ｷｯﾁﾘ 教えたげる｡
ええ～｡
Ow, ow, ouch!
最初に ﾌﾞﾗｼをかけて
髪についた汚れを取って
Next, wet your hair thoroughly with warm water.
って もう濡らしちゃってるから
遅いけど 今度からね｡
Now, in your palm, work the shampoo into a lather...
うぇ いててて…｡
それから お湯をかけて
しっかり髪全体を濡らすの｡
Then gently massage the product into your scalp.
ｼｬﾝﾌﾟｰは よく泡立ててから｡
Try not to scrub too hard, though.
優しくもむように｡
うぅ…｡
After that, rinse thoroughly.
ｺﾞｼｺﾞｼこすっちゃ ﾀﾞﾒだからね｡
ん んん…｡
With long hair like this,
it should take around five minutes.
Five minutes? Are you serious?!
すすぎは きちんと！
この長さなら ５分はほしいかな｡
５分？ うそだろ!?
ううう…｡
It's finally over.
ううぅ～｡
ううう…｡
(鐘の音)
And for the final touch...
A leave-in treatment for the ends!
やっと終わった…｡
What? You're kidding, right?
えっ？
それから毛先に
じっくり ﾄﾘｰﾄﾒﾝﾄを！
Somebody help!
えっ？ おい うそだろ！
ひぃい…｡
Now we can finally relax in the tub.
助けて～！
(いびき)
It's bad manners to soak your hair in the water, remember?
ふぅ…｡ んん～！
やっと 湯舟に入れたよ～｡
You'll be chilly after all the hair care,
but a good, long soak will warm you back—
湯舟に髪をつけるのは
ﾏﾅｰ違反だからね｡
Enough!
What?!
But we just got in!
髪を洗ってる間に
I'll wait for you in the lobby!
冷えちゃった身体を
ちゃんと温めて…｡
もう出る！
ええ～!?
Honestly...
まだ早いよ～｡
ﾛﾋﾞｰで待ってるからな！
ふんん…｡
No wonder girls take ages in the bath.
もお～！
女子の風呂が長いわけだよ…｡
(ﾌﾀが開く音)
Now, that hits the spot!
(ｺｰﾋｰ牛乳を飲む音)
ぶひぃ～！ やっぱこれだな～！
Still, it's been ages since we bathed together like that, huh?
んっ…｡
Come on, hold still!
(飲む音)
Get back here!
ん…｡
しかし
今さら妹と風呂に入るとは…｡
You'll catch a cold if you don't dry your hair!
んっ？
こら 待ってて！
(笑い声)
(じゃれあう声)
I'm gonna start rinsing now.
Keep your eyes shut, okay?
あ…｡
拭かないと 風邪ひくだろ～｡
Okay!
I used to help her bathe all the time when we were kids.
お湯かけるぞ～｡
目 しっかりつぶってろ～｡
Okay, all done!
うん！
Thanks, Onii-chan!
《小さいころは
よく入れてやったっけ…》
はい 終わり！
んん…｡
Now, it looks like...
ありがとう お兄ちゃん！
(まひろ/みはり)ﾌﾌｯ！
ああ～！
she's the one helping me.
それが今や…｡
Mihari's grown up so much since then, too.
Thanks, Onii-chan!
I mean...
If this keeps up, it's kinda like...
She won't be my "little" sister anymore...
入れられる立場に…｡
みはりも成長したもんだ～｡
Onii-cha—
Mahiro-chan?
やれやれ これはもうあれだな～｡
ありがとう お兄ちゃん！
Oh, there you are!
妹っていうより…｡
Sorry for the wait!
"Mahiro-chan"?
お兄ちゃ…｡
ん～？
あっ…｡
Well, we're out in public, you know?
まひろちゃ～ん？
んっ？
おっ いたいた～！ お待たせ～｡
｢まひろちゃん｣？
I can't call you "Onii-chan" here, can I?
I guess you're right.
いや～ 人前だしさ
｢お兄ちゃん｣はちょっと…｡
Well, let's head home!
はあ…｡ ﾌｯ それもそっか｡
Onee-chan!
じゃ 帰ろう！
んっ？
(戸を閉める音)
O-O-Onee-chan...
Whoa, there!
ﾌｯ ｢お姉ちゃん｣！
I was just playing along!
Onee-chan...
はう！ お お ｢お姉ちゃん｣…｡
That settles it. Let's come here again, okay?
Q-Quit it!
おい ﾉﾘでやっただけだぞ！
ｲｯﾋﾋﾋ…｡
Get off of me!
Pat, pat, pat.
｢お姉ちゃん｣…｡
Stop stroking my hair!
うんうん また来ようね～！
It's still damp...
や やめろ！ 離れろ～！
よしよし～｡
なでるな～！
I think it's high time your big sis taught you how to dry your hair properly.
あ 生乾き…｡
This is torture!
ふぅ ここはお姉ちゃんが
正しい乾かし方を じっくりと…｡
I
Onimai.
MA
NI
O
ひいぃ！ もうこりごりだ～！
I'm sleepy.
Onii-chan! Breakfast is ready!
(鳥のさえずり)
Coming!
眠い…｡
お兄ちゃん！
朝ごはんできてるよ～｡
Wait, Onii-chan!
Your hair's soaking wet!
ふぇ～い…｡
Ugh.
I can't help it. It gets wet every time I wash my face.
んっ？ ちょっとお兄ちゃん！
Goodness. That's why you should wear this.
髪の毛 びしょびしょ！
ｹﾞｯ…｡
顔洗うとき
どうしても濡れんだよぉ｡
Hm, this thing's kinda neat.
もう…
そういうときはこうやって…｡
Right?
Wow, girls have so many cool items in their inventory.
Like this, and bras, and stuff.
うん～ これは便利だな～｡
でしょ！
Stop talking like we're in a video game.
Try to take hair care more seriously from now on, okay?
女子は 装備が充実してるよな～｡
これとか ﾌﾞﾗとかさ～｡
Hair is a crucial part of girlish self-expression, you know?
装備って ｹﾞｰﾑじゃないんだから｡
Yeah, yeah.
これからは 髪の毛の
お手入れもちゃんとしてね｡
｢髪は女の命｣って言うでしょ｡
This is pretty good.
はいはい｡
ﾌｯ…｡
Man, I'm stuffed!
(食べる音)
ﾌｯ…｡
ん… んっ うまいな｡
はむっ！
I wonder when I last ate a proper breakfast like this.
んっ ﾌﾌｯ…｡
ぶふ～ 満足満足～！
朝ﾒｼ ちゃんと食うなんて
いつぶりだろうな～｡
Oh, it's just a mirror.
I guess Mihari must have put it here.
うおっ！
なんだ 鏡か～｡
Hair care, huh?
さては みはりが出してきたな～？
ん…｡
There.
All done!
手入れねぇ…｡
Crap! What the hell am I doing?!
My goodness, how cute!
よし できた～！
って 何やってんだ ｵﾚ…｡
It's just, you know, it's been getting hot out recently.
でぇ!?
んっ？
(みはりの鼻歌)
ﾔﾀﾞ！ かわいい！
ひゃああ～！
So I thought I'd try putting my hair up like you saw, and well...
I started trying a bunch of styles and got kind of into it.
いや その…
最近暑くなってきただろ～｡
だから さっきみたいに
髪をまとめようと思ってさ…｡
You have some of the most random talents, Onii-chan.
Comes from playing video games.
My hand-eye coordination is—
いろいろ試しているうちに
Wait! I have an idea.
なんだか
だんだん楽しくなってきて…｡
Let's document our findings!
変なところで器用ね お兄ちゃん｡
Huh?!
Starting with buns.
ｹﾞｰﾑで鍛えてるからな！
So cute!
手先の動きならまっ…｡
そうだ ちょうどいいわ！
Y-You think so?
ちゃんと 記録しておきましょ！
へっ？
Now for a sporty ponytail!
まずはお団子ﾍｱ！ かわいい！
(ｼｬｯﾀｰ音)
You look adorable!
Okay, next!
そ そうか～？
(ｼｬｯﾀｰ音)
Twintails! A classic!
ｽﾎﾟｰﾃｨｰな ﾎﾟﾆｰﾃｰﾙ！
(ｼｬｯﾀｰ音)
Stunning!
これも似合う！ 続けて続けて！
(ｼｬｯﾀｰ音)
ﾌｯﾌｰﾝ！
Why not add some cat ears, too?
やっぱり定番 ﾂｲﾝﾃｰﾙ！
(ｼｬｯﾀｰ音)
Come on, Onii-chan! Strike a pose!
こっちも素敵～！
(ｼｬｯﾀｰ音)
Huh? What pose?
Don't think, just do! You got this, Mahiro-chan!
ﾆﾋﾋ～！
(ｼｬｯﾀｰ音)
Uh— But I don't—
ついでに 猫耳も！
うおっ！ うっ…｡
(ｼｬｯﾀｰ音)
You're beautiful! Captivating! Absolutely adorable!
お兄ちゃん！
うぇ…｡
ほら ﾎﾟｰｽﾞﾎﾟｰｽﾞ！
Now pose like a cat!
えっ？ ﾎﾟｰｽﾞ？
大丈夫 できるよ まひろちゃん！
L-Like a cat?!
R-Right meow?
えらい！ すごい！ かわいい！
ええぇ!?
猫のﾎﾟｰｽﾞ！
ね ねこ!?
Hold it!
What am I, your puppet?!
Oh dear.
こ こうかにゃ～？
Wh-What have I become?
(連続ｼｬｯﾀｰ音)
When did my feminine side become so second nature to me?
って な～にやらせんだ！
あら～｡
Excellent.
お おそろしい…｡
I've noticed there's less friction with your new wardrobe now, too.
いつの間にか
自然に｢女の子してる｣自分が…｡
Dressing up feels good, doesn't it?
Th-That's not...
よきよき～｡
うっ…｡
Besides, look who's talking!
このところ すっかり
お着替えにも慣れたみたいだし｡
How can you say that when you basically wear the same outfit every day?!
ｵｼｬﾚするのって 楽しいでしょ｡
Th-That's different.
そ そんなことは…｡
んっ？
This is like my uniform.
だいたい お前！
人にそう言うわりには
My trademark outfit, if you will.
Why don't you try dressing up for a change?!
いつも
似たような格好じゃないか！
What?!
わ 私はいいのよ…｡
H-How dare you?! This is rich coming from you!
これ 制服みたいなもんだし
ﾄﾚｰﾄﾞﾏｰｸ的な？
Just you watch!
たまには ｵｼｬﾚでもしたらどうだ！
はあ～!?
こ この兄… どの口で…｡
見てなさい！ ﾌﾝｯ！
～
(扉の開閉音)
ん… は…｡
ﾌｯ…｡
W-Well?
は… うぅ…｡ んっ｡
Hmm?
A-Are you happy now?
(扉の開閉音)
Wha?
ど どう～？
ん んあ？
Oh... sure.
こ これでいいでしょ～？
Ouch!
えっ？ あ はい｡
What was that fo—
Hey! I didn't do anything!
(ﾀｲﾋﾟﾝｸﾞ音)
ふん！
あいた！
ONIMAI
Onimai.
何すんだ…｡ ぶっ！
ぶなあ なんだよ～！
Onimeow.
ONIMAI
おにみゃい…｡
You even sit differently.
(ｹﾞｰﾑ音)
ﾆｨ…｡
んっ？
My goodness.
You've really gotten into the swing of things, huh?
女の子座り｡
んっ…｡
It's just, that position feels more natural in this body, somehow.
ふぇ うわああ！
あらあら いよいよ女の子が
板についてきたんじゃない？
Not good! This is not good!
ん…｡
ﾌｯ…｡
いや なぜかこの身体だと
あのほうが楽で… はっ！
I'm gonna reclaim my masculinity!
いかん いかんぞ！
...is what I'd like to say, but...
What does it mean to be...
ふん！
masculine?
Oh, dear.
ｵﾚは男らしさを取り戻す！
Well, let's see. First things first...
とは言ったのものの…
男らしさ とは？
Someone who's strong.
Strong!
Reliable.
やれやれ…｡
Reliable!
Able to whisk someone off their feet.
そうね… まずは たくましい｡
たくましい！
Ouch.
頼りになって｡
頼りになって！
お姫様抱っことか｡
H-How about a piggyback?
Here I go!
んん～！
いだあ！
う うぅ…｡
むう お おんぶなら…｡
Okay, let's sumo-wrestle!
いくぞ～！ ふん！
ぶおっ！
うわ…｡
ぶへぇ！
Bring it!
んん…｡
うう うぇ…｡
Fine, we settle this with video games!
相撲だ 相撲！
What does that have to do with masculinity?
ふんふん！ 来い！
あ あああ… あ…｡
じゃあ ｹﾞｰﾑで勝負だ！
I think you should be worrying less about masculinity
もう男らしさ 関係なくない？
and more about setting a routine for yourself.
Fine.
Getting up at a set time every day,
ﾌｯ お兄ちゃんの場合
moderating video game time,
男らしさの前に
まずは規則正しい生活でしょ｡
building up an exercise regimen...
Exercise...
はい…｡
毎日決まった時間に起きて
That's it!
ｹﾞｰﾑは ほどほどに
少しずつ運動もして…｡
Strength training!
Whoops-a-daisy.
運動…｡ はっ！
そうだ 筋ﾄﾚだ！
わっとっと！
んい…｡
ん～？
I tried.
Wait... what?!
ふぐ…｡
Were you trying to do a sit-up?!
If you wanna exercise, you'll need to try a little harder than that.
んんっ！
ﾀﾞﾒだ～｡
えっ 何？ 今のもしかして腹筋!?
Ow, ow, ow. I think I sprained something.
あのね…
どうせなら もっとまじめに…｡
You can't be serious.
う… うひぃ…｡
No, really...
I'm starting to feel kinda funny, too.
いててて… 早速 筋肉痛が｡
んな ｱﾎな…｡
いや… これ なんか気分まで
悪くなってきたような…｡
What? What's wrong?
Onii-chan?!
ぐ ぐふぅ…｡
え ちょっと？
お兄ちゃん!?
I feel a lot better now, actually.
(呼吸音)
Thank goodness!
だいぶﾏｼになったかも…｡
H-Hey! Don't cry!
はっ！ は…｡
It's not that big a deal.
よかった～！
I-I can't help it!
(泣く声)
I worried what I'd do without you, you know?!
ふぇ お おい｡
泣くなよ 大げさだなぁ｡
だ だって～！
お兄ちゃんに
何かあったらって思うと…｡
What even was that, anyway?
It doesn't feel like I have a cold or anything.
(すすり泣き)
Don't tell me!
ﾌﾌｯ…｡
You don't think it's a side effect of that medicine you gave me?!
けど なんだこれ…｡
風邪って感じでもなさそうだし｡
No, I swear I took all the necessary precautions.
まさか！
例の薬のせいじゃないだろうな！
And besides,
it'd be strange for side effects to suddenly occur almost a month in.
えっ？ う～ん…｡
いや でも安全性は
十分に検証したし…｡
A month?
第一 女の子になって
一か月近く経ってから
副反応が現れるっていうのも…｡
んっ？ 一か月？
あ…｡
Um...
んん～｡
Do you happen to have any other symptoms?
Like what?
ああ…｡
Feeling sleepy?
I'd say so.
ええと…
ほかに気になることとかない？
Sluggish?
Yup.
Kinda low-energy? A bit down in the dumps?
気になること？
眠いとか｡
眠いな｡
Excuse you! Don't bad-mouth the home security officer!
だるいとか｡
だるい｡
I'm not! Just listen, okay?
気分が落ち気味で
ｼｬｷｯとしないとか｡
むっ！ なんだよ！
自宅警備員を悪く言うな！
Do your breasts feel swollen at all?
My breasts?
違うって！ よく聞いて！
Now that you mention it,
they do feel a little tender.
ｺﾎﾝ｡
ん～？
胸が張るとかはない？
ん 胸？
What about your tummy?
Do you feel like you have an upset stomach?
ん… ん～？
Yeah, you're right! I do!
そう言われれば
たしかに ちょっと痛いような｡
Y-You know, Onii-chan...
お腹は？
お腹壊したときみたいな痛みとか｡
I don't wanna scare you or anything, but...
あ そうそう！ そんな感じ！
うぇ…｡
I think you might be on your—
Ugh, it's starting to hurt again.
あ あのね お兄ちゃん…｡
とても
言いにくいことなんだけど…｡
たぶん お兄ちゃんの身体は…｡
Sorry, I gotta go to the bathroom.
また痛みが…｡
あ…｡
うふっ～｡
う… ごめん 先にﾄｲﾚ…｡
W-Wait!
ふ… うぃ…｡
What is it?
Um... Well... Err...
ん…｡
ま 待って！
はあ…｡
J-Just try not to freak out, okay?
なんだよ…｡
あの… その… ええとぉ…｡
と とにかく 気をたしかにね！
What's she so worked up about, anyway?
ﾌﾌｯ…｡
(扉が開く音)
ん～？
I've been to the bathroom plenty of times.
なんなんだ みはりのﾔﾂ…｡
今さら ﾄｲﾚくらいで
あんな慌てて…｡
ああ～｡
んっ？ んん～？
ん… んんん…｡
(地鳴り)
うわあああ～！
That's it. This is the end.
(犬の鳴き声)
Hey, Onii-chan...{I don't think it's clear whether she would need to explain anything right now. Better to keep it vague.}
(嗚咽)
I had my whole life ahead of me.
Listen to me.
ｵﾚはもうおしまいだ…｡
If I had only known, I would've finished that game sooner.
あのね お兄ちゃん…｡
短い人生だった…｡
だから…｡
Mihari, it's up to you now.
こんなことなら 早くあのｹﾞｰﾑ
ｸﾘｱしとけばよかった…｡
うぅ… みはり～
あとはお前に託したぞ｡
Onii-chan.
あ… うぅ～｡
Here, this'll warm up your tummy.
(嗚咽)
お兄ちゃん｡
ううぅ… ひっ｡
It should help with the pain.
ふえぇ…｡
はい これでお腹あっためて｡
あ… ああ…｡
Light stretching can be helpful, too.
そしたら 少し楽になるからね｡
We can do some together once the pain settles down a bit.
はあ…｡
ゆっくりｽﾄﾚｯﾁをしても
いいらしいよ｡
落ち着いたら 一緒にやろうね｡
あ…｡
Note: Rice with azuki beans, typically served on
auspicious occasions—including a girl's first menstruation
I also brought some sekihan...{https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sekihan?oldid=491511711 -- " In some places it is customarily made when a young woman reaches menarche"}{CR has "I also brought a ready meal, if you'd like," and although I don't know what the heck a ready meal is, that's what she says. Maybe I can change it to something that makes it more clear what a  レトルト is. Whatever. The bigger issue is that the point of this line is going to go over everyone's head. The point is not the type of food prep, it's that it's this sekihan/red rice stuff. Therefore, I localized the line by nuking the english and introducing japanese that is nowhere to be found in the dialogue, which is stupid, but the point is that it gives people something to google, and it signals to them "you need to know what this is to understand the joke." With any accurate/mechanical translation, the viewer is going to be wondering why the heck mahiro reacts to the line angrily.}{ok, i guess if you're talking the "go google it" approach, you may as well do a TL note}
No, thank you!
ﾌﾌｯ…｡
あ…｡
ﾚﾄﾙﾄなら あるけど…｡
いるか！
(鳥のさえずり)
ん… んぃ…｡
Did you put it on properly?
I think so.
う… ううぅ…｡
あ… ちゃんとつけられた？
たぶん…｡
It feels kinda... awkward.
ﾋﾋ…｡
～
Do you guys really wear these things?
なんか ｺﾞﾜｺﾞﾜする…｡
うぅ…｡
They're so uncomfortable.
女子って
ﾎﾝﾄにこんなのつけてんの？
You'll get used to it.
I don't know...
ん… 違和感すごいんだけど…｡
You complain, but don't guys have—
んん…｡
Have what?
Don't guys have a foreign object to contend with too?
すぐ慣れるって｡
ﾎﾝﾄかな～｡
Below the waist, I mean.
それを言うなら 男子だって…
あっ…｡
Don't call it that!
んっ？ なんだよ｡
How do you normally keep it under control?
男子だって 異物があるじゃない｡
お腹の下に…｡
What?!
How can you ask such a thing?!
You're such a pervert, Mihari-chan!
えっ！ 異物って言うな！
Honestly!
普段 どうやってしまってるの？
It's because you were complaining about it being uncomfortable!
ひぃい！ 何てこと聞くんだ！
No, it's just...
みはりちゃんの えっち～！
はっ！ もう！
うわああ！
Anyway, I never knew you were going through this every month.
お兄ちゃんが
違和感とかって言うからでしょ！
いや～ ｱﾊﾊﾊ｡
And all without whining about it once.
ｱﾊﾊ…｡
What a trooper.
しかし みはりも毎月
こんな思いしてたんだな｡
Well!
Next time your tummy's hurting,
let your big brother know, okay?
泣き言も言わずに
大したもんだ えらいえらい｡
I'll be there for you in a heart... beat...
あ…｡
Eek!
ま でもこれからお腹痛いときは
兄ちゃんに言うんだぞ｡
Wh-Wh-What did I do this time?!
Have some tact!
しっかり看病してやるから な…｡
いいいぃ～!?
With a one-two-three, it's time to play
な なななな なんでだよ～！
ﾃﾞﾘｶｼｰ！
Come and join us in a secret hideaway
ふぎゃ！
(電子ﾚﾝｼﾞの音)
Hey, br- I mean, Mahiro! Wanna try on a maid outfit?
Huh?
No, it's gotta be a bunny-girl costume!
H-Hold on!
Let's go with a dress, we can even match!
Point is, it's time to strip!
Hey! Cut it out!
Noooooooooo!
A genius has at a docile lab rat
(And in the night...)
A single dose, perfection isn't slow!
(Hey, what the heck?)
Cutie acquired, cuddles required
Partner recaptured, hey, let's go!
(Oh, deary me!)
(Time for a show)
Let's have a sleepover, yay, yay, yay!
(And someone's gonna feel like they're the odd one out!)
The girls got a little somethin' goin' on tonight
(Send help, I don't know how to feel)
With a one-two-three, it's time to play
And break the gender barrier
Soon enough your heart's athrob
Time to welcome you into a place you've never known!
(One! Two!)
(It's a bouncy world!)
It's time to reassess! No more stress!
Just submit, surrender, don't obsess!
Girls with itty-bitty bodies can still
Be packed with secrets deep within!
Give your all, have a ball!
Right until the cards'll start to fall!
There's one thing that you really should know:
Girl power makes the world go 'round!
If there's an identity crisis coming on, it can wait another day
Illustration: Yoneyama Mai
Next Episode: Mahiro's Close Encounter
See you next time!